excellent-hosts.com 2011-03-14

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting Excellent-Hosts.Com, a free site. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the collection and use of the personal information you submit on Web pages where this policy is posted.

**The Information We Collect**

At sites, you can enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, and information about your interests in.

At certain parts of some of our sites, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to programs, and services, or otherwise participate in the site's activities and offerings. We also collect certain non-personally identifiable information.

**How We Use The Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself to fulfil your requests for our free sites that we believe may be of interest to you.

We use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to fulfil a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us.

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities.

We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

**How You Can Access or Correct Information**

To access the personally identifiable information that this free site has collected about you online from the pages on which this Privacy Policy is posted, to correct factual errors in such information, or to update your interests, preferences or other portions of your user profile, please send an email to  **[webmaster@excellent-hosts.com](mailto:webmaster@excellent-hosts.com) **

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Children's Privacy**

Visitors to this site may participate in many activities without providing any personally identifiable information. However, if a user wants to participate in certain of our interactive features, we ask the user to register and provide us with the following information: the user's e-mail address and age information. When the person who registers indicates that he or she is under 13, we will either collect no personally identifiable information from that individual or inform the child that a parent's verifiable consent is required or we will collect the e-mail address of the user's parent in addition to the user's e-mail address. We use the parent's e-mail address to seek the parent's verifiable consent or notify the parent of his/her child's online activities and enable the parent to unsubscribe his/her child from a newsletter or other similar activity. If a user is under 13, we will not condition his/her participation in an online activity on the disclosure of more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. We do not share children's information with outside third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy.

**Notification Regarding Updates**

From time to time, we may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it.
